There are some relationships so taboo they're irresistible.
Close My Eyes is a drama, romance film directed by Stephen Poliakoff.
After some years of tension, Richard begins a sexual
relationship with his sister Natalie.
Now married, the relationship proves dangerously obsessional.
Sinclair, played by Alan Rickman.
Richard, played by Clive Owen.
Natalie Bryant, played by Saskia Reeves.
Colin, played by Karl Johnson.
Jessica, played by Lesley Sharp.
Paula, played by Kate Gartside.
Close My Eyes is a 1991 British drama film written and directed by Stephen Poliakoff and starring
Alan Rickman, Clive Owen and Saskia Reeves as well as Lesley Sharp and Karl Johnson.
Music was by Michael Gibbs and the film was produced for
Beambright and FilmFour International by Therese Pickard.
It had a limited theatrical release from 6 September 1991, before being
shown in Channel 4's Film on Four strand on 28 October 1993.
The film explores themes of river thames, wheelchair,
marriage, forbidden love, based on play or musical.
The tone is emotional.